https://sciencex.com/help/terms/

Terms of Use
These Terms of Use and Privacy Policy govern your use of Science X and its network ('Science X'),
including all of the products, services, and websites (phys.org, medicalxpress.com, techxplore.com), any subdomains of those websites, mobile sites, apps, and APIs.
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.
Access to and use of this site is provided by the Science X subject to the following terms:
By using Science X you agree to be legally bound by these terms, which shall take effect immediately on your first use of Science X.
If you do not agree to be legally bound by all the following terms please do not access and/or use Science X.
The Science X may change these terms at any time by posting changes online.
Please review these terms regularly to ensure you are aware of any changes made by the Science X.
Your continued use of Science X after changes are posted means you agree to be legally bound by these terms as updated and/or amended.
Use of Science X
You may not copy, reproduce, republish, download, post, broadcast, transmit, make available to the public, or otherwise use Science X
content in any way except for your own personal, non-commercial use. You also agree not to adapt, alter or create a derivative work from
any Science X content except for your own personal, non-commercial use.
Students, teachers and professors are free to use, reproduce articles and copy Science X
content for academic purposes without obtaining prior written approval.
The only request is users shall provide a credit and source URL link of the original Science X article.
Any other use of Science X content requires the prior written
permission of the Science X. If you would like to request permission to use any of the content on our sites,
please review our copyright notice.
Our site contains content that we create as well as content provided by third parties.
This content includes, among other things, product reviews and services offered by parties other than Science X.
We do not guarantee the accuracy, the integrity, or the quality of the content on our sites, and you may not rely on any of this content.
Without limitation, we are not responsible for postings by users in the user opinion, message board, or feedback sections of our sites.
You may be exposed to content that you find offensive, indecent, or objectionable or that is inaccurate, and you bear all risks
associated with using that content. We have the right, but not the obligation, to remove any content that may, in our sole discretion,
violate these Terms or that is otherwise objectionable.
You agree to use Science X only for lawful purposes, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of,
restrict or inhibit anyone else's use and enjoyment of Science X. Prohibited behavior includes harassing or causing
distress or inconvenience to any person, transmitting obscene or offensive content or disrupting the normal flow of dialogue within Science X.
Age requirement for Science X Account
Due to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Science X Account is available only for individuals who are over thirteen (13) years of age.
Science X is relying on your representation that you are at least 13 years of age.
Children under the age of 13 may not sign up for Science X Account and parents or legal guardians may not enter into to this Agreement on their behalf.
Disclaimers and Limitation of Liability
While Science X tries hard to ensure that these websites are functioning correctly and are as accurate as possible,
this will not always be achievable and therefore the following disclaimer applies.
Science X content, including the information, names, images, pictures, logos and icons regarding or relating to the Science X,
its products and services (or to third party products and services), is provided "AS IS" and on an "IS AVAILABLE" basis without any
representations or any kind of warranty made.
Science X does not guarantee or represent that the content and/or facilities available or accessible via these websites will
always be accurate, complete or current or that access to the websites will be uninterrupted.
Science X expressly disclaims all liability for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage occasioned from the use
or inability to use these websites, whether directly or indirectly resulting from inaccuracies, defects, viruses, errors -
whether typographical or otherwise, omissions, out of date information or otherwise.
Accessing these websites and the downloading of material from them is done entirely at the user's own risk.
The user, and not Science X, will be entirely responsible for any resulting damage to software or computer systems and/or
any resulting loss of data even if Science X has been advised of the possibility of such damage.
Science X makes no representations whatsoever about any third party websites which you may access.
When you access a third party website via this website, please understand that it is independent from Science X,
and that Science X has no control over the content on that website. In addition, a link from this website to a third party
website does not mean that we endorse or accept responsibility for the content, the privacy practices, or the use of such website.
It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you access is free of items such as viruses, worms,
Trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature.
We have the right, but not the obligation, to take any of the following actions in
our sole discretion at any time and for any reason without giving you any prior notice:
Restrict, suspend, or terminate your access to all or any part of our Services;
Change, suspend, or discontinue all or any part of our Services;
Refuse, move, or remove any material that you submit to our sites for any reason;
Refuse, move, or remove any content that is available on our sites;
Deactivate or delete your accounts and all related information and files in your account;
Establish general practices and limits concerning use of our sites.
Medical disclaimer
Information provided on Science X is for educational and informational purposes only and may not be construed as medical advice.
Please refer to the full text of the Medical Disclaimer.
Intellectual property
The names, images and logos identifying the Science X or third parties and
their products and services are subject to copyright, design rights and trade marks of the Science X and/or third parties.
Nothing contained in these terms shall be construed as conferring by implication, estoppel or otherwise any licence or right to use any trademark,
patent, design right or copyright of the Science X or any other third party.
Contributions to Science X
Where you are invited to submit any contribution to Science X (including any text,
photographs, graphics, video or audio) you agree, by submitting your contribution,
to grant the Science X a perpetual, royalty-free, non-exclusive, sub-licenseable right and license to use,
reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform, play, make available to the public,
and exercise all copyright and publicity rights with respect to your contribution worldwide and/or to incorporate your contribution in
other works in any media now known or later developed for the full term of any rights that may exist in your contribution, and in accordance
with privacy restrictions set out in the Science X's privacy policy. If you do not want to grant to the Science X
the rights set out above, please do not submit your contribution to Science X.
Further, by submitting your contribution to Science X, you:
warrant that your contribution:
is your own original work and that you have the right to make it available to the Science X for all the purposes specified above;
is not defamatory; and
does not infringe any law; and
indemnify the Science X against all legal fees, damages and other expenses that may be incurred by the Science X as a result of your breach of the above warranty; and
waive any moral rights in your contribution for the purposes of its submission to and publication on Science X and the purposes specified above.
General
These terms shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the European Union.
Privacy policy
All of the information that we collect from you
is subject to our privacy policy.
Please click here to see our full privacy policy.
Corrections and retractions
Science X policy on corrections and retractions can be found here.
Questions?
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
Updated: October 1, 2020
